<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Offensive Cybersecurity - Category - Raptor Blog</title><link>https://blog.anthares101.com/categories/offensive-cybersecurity/</link><description>Offensive Cybersecurity - Category - Raptor Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.anthares101.com/categories/offensive-cybersecurity/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to setup the Flipper Zero for Wi-Fi attacks</title><link>https://blog.anthares101.com/how-to-setup-the-flipper-zero-for-wi-fi-attacks/</link><pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Anthares101</author><guid>https://blog.anthares101.com/how-to-setup-the-flipper-zero-for-wi-fi-attacks/</guid><description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/images/banner.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>How to setup the Flipper Zero for Wi-Fi attacks Before starting, remember that performing any of the attacks explained in this post to networks without previous consent is illegal, this post information is for educational purposes only.
Introduction You may be thinking: &ldquo;I just buy the Wi-Fi Flipper board and call it a day&rdquo; well, not really. Even buying the Flipper Wi-Fi Devboard instead of making a custom module won&rsquo;t enable the Flipper to start de-authenticating people out of the box, you will need to flash the proper firmware.]]></description></item><item><title>DNS tunneling</title><link>https://blog.anthares101.com/dns-tunneling/</link><pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Anthares101</author><guid>https://blog.anthares101.com/dns-tunneling/</guid><description>&lt;div class="featured-image">
&lt;img src="/images/banner.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
&lt;/div>DNS tunneling The idea of this technique is to use the DNS protocol to route all the traffic, just like a VPN! Of course this method will make your connection slower but will allow you to bypass certain systems like network filters or captive portals. Obviously, you could use this to exfiltrate data too.
The reason why this works is that normally when captive portals or firewalls rules are setup, the administrators block all TCP and UDP connections when certain rule is met but they forget about checking DNS queries.</description></item><item><title>Attacking Wi-Fi networks with Aircrack-ng</title><link>https://blog.anthares101.com/attacking-wi-fi-networks-with-aircrack-ng/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><author>Anthares101</author><guid>https://blog.anthares101.com/attacking-wi-fi-networks-with-aircrack-ng/</guid><description>&lt;div class="featured-image">
&lt;img src="/images/banner.jpg" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
&lt;/div>Attacking Wi-Fi networks with Aircrack-ng Before starting, remember that performing any of the attacks explained in this post to networks without previous consent is illegal, this post information is for educational purposes only.
Introduction Wi-Fi uses management frames (datagrams are called frames in this context) and data frames. Only data frames are encrypted and injecting them into the network will require a previous association with the AP. This is not necessary for management frames or if we send data frames spoofing some of the clients MAC addresses.</description></item></channel></rss>